octro.com 2011-05-26

# Octro

#### Copyright 

Copyright (c) 2006, 2007 Octro, Inc. 

No portion of the Octro, Inc. WWW sites may be copied or redistributed in any manner without the express written consent of Octro, Inc.

#### Trademark 

Octro, OctroTalk, all other Octro software title names and their respective logos are trademarks of Octro Inc.

Google, Google Talk and Gmail are the trademarks or registered trademarks of Google Inc or its subsidiaries. All other marks and product names may be the trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. 

This web site, any Octro software and any Octro service are in no way affiliated with or endorsed by America Online, Inc. or ICQ, Inc. The marks AOL and AIM are registered trademarks of America Online, Inc.; the marks Instant Messenger and AOL Instant Messenger are service marks of America Online, Inc.; the mark ICQ is a registered mark of ICQ, Inc.

#### Privacy Policy

The Privacy Policy describes how we treat your personal information when you use OctroTalk and other applications and services from Octro Inc. 

At Octro Inc., we respect your right to privacy. We will never sell or otherwise pass on your name, e-mail or other information to a third party without your consent except for when it is required to provide you the service you are using or when it is required by law.

**What information do we collect?** When you use software or services from Octro, we collect some personal information to allow us to provide you the service, fulfill your requirement and provide you the customer support. This information may include your account information for Google, MSN, AOL, ICQ and other networks, your name, address, phone number, your device information, registration data, email address, and any other information that you entered while using our software and services. We do not store the credit card information. 

**How is this information used?** Only Octro has access to any such information. We will not give or sell your private information to any other company for any purpose without your written consent, except if required by law. We may use this information to notify you of important announcements regarding our software developments, software upgrades and special offers and provide you the application/software support. If you do not want to receive any announcement from us, you can ask to be excluded from such announcements by sending us email to this effect. 

**Review of personal information.** At any time, you may ask us to remove your registration data and personal information our system. However, some information may be necessary for providing you our services and support. In that event we may not be able to provide you one or more of our services that you are using. 

**Security.** Octro will take reasonable steps to protect your personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or unauthorized alteration.

**Proper and Legal Use.** When the end user (that is you) downloads and/or uses any of our software or services he is responsible for his own communications and for any consequences thereof. He must use the software or any of its part or the service in compliance with all applicable local, state, national, and international laws, rules and regulations, including any laws regarding the transmission of technical data and export control laws. You shall not, shall not agree to, and shall not authorize or encourage any third party to:  
(i)   use the software or service to upload, transmit or otherwise distribute any content that is unlawful, defamatory, harassing, abusive, fraudulent, obscene, contains viruses, or is otherwise objectionable;  
(ii)   upload, transmit or otherwise distribute content that infringes upon another party's intellectual property rights or other proprietary, contractual or fiduciary rights or obligations;  
(iii)   prevent others from using the software or the service;  
(iv)   use the software or the service for any fraudulent or inappropriate purpose.

#### Refund Policy 

All software from Octro can be downloaded as a free trial from our web site. We encourage all users to thoroughly test any software title that they wish to license and satisfy themselves fully that it works to their satisfaction before purchasing. The license is not transferable except in the first year of license period. In the first year, the user is allowed to switch devices upto 5 times. Octro Inc does not offer refunds. There are no exceptions to this policy.
